{
    "subject": "resource/Thomas_Pendelton",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Anaheim,_California",
    "human_readable": "Thomas Pendelton was born in Anaheim, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9127485156059265,
            "question": "Where was Thomas Pendelton born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8897597789764404,
            "question": "What state was Thomas Pendelton born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8387656807899475,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Thomas Pendelton was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8112089037895203,
            "question": "What year was Thomas Pendelton born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7562867403030396,
            "question": "Where might Thomas Pendelton have lived besides Anaheim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3850754201412201,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Thomas Pendelton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3571051359176636,
            "question": "Do you know anything about Thomas Pendelton's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3284527659416199,
            "question": "Is Anaheim a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21364818513393402,
            "question": "Is Anaheim a popular place to live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14296197891235352,
            "question": "What is California known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Thomas Pendelton was born in Anaheim, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8190_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Anaheim a popular place to live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8190_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Anaheim a city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8190_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know anything about Thomas Pendelton's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8190_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8190_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8190_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8190_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8190_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8190_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8190_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8190_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8190_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8190_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8190_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the document with file path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8190/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt explicitly states that Thomas Pendelton was born in Anaheim, California."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Thomas Pendelton was born in Anaheim, California,\" which matches the information in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}